are you a current GP user wondering what
a move to the cloud and business Central
might look like but aren't sure where to
start sign up today for a free and easy
GP assessment the assessment provides
guidance and Direction on what your
journey will look
like the assessment was designed with a
few main tenants it needed to be super
easy to use fast and non-intrusive and
finally free and available to everyone
there's no need to wait for nights and
weekends to run the assessment as it can
be done during business business hours
While others are working in GP it also
doesn't require that you've already
purchased a BC license the assessment
tool only reads data from the GP SQL
Server nothing is ever written or
changed to your GP system after the
assessment is run using the assessment
removes the need for lengthy surveys and
numerous meetings simply run the tool
view your results and share them with
your partner let's take a closer
look the first step is to fill out a
quick signup form after submitting your
information you will receive an email
with a link to a page where you can
download the
tool once you log in simply select the
download button and copy your unique
token after you've launched the
assessment paste in your token and
select next now entering a user that has
access to GP SQL Server choose connect
and select the companies you want to
assess as a best practice it's
recommended that you not include test or
sample companies
now run the assessment after all tasks
have been complete you can easily review
the information captured by the tool
before sending once you've reviewed the
information select the send results
button when your results have been
analyzed you will receive another email
with a link to your assessment
report your assessment report will look
similar to this where you can review
modules and features that are being used
in GP drill into any isv solutions you
have installed and review any potential
migration risk identified by the
assessment don't worry though each risk
includes more details and
recommendations on how to fix remember
to click the share icon to share the
assessment Report with your
partner now that you've had an
opportunity to learn more about the GP
assessment start your journey today by
going out to BC migration
assessments. to learn more about
business Central check out the GP tobc
YouTube playlist to view short videos
that show how common activities done in
GP can perform be performed in business
Central want to see business Central in
action check out a guided tour or learn
more at business Central learning
courses at BC learn